# **ANGEL TORRES**

Las Vegas, NV 89081 ◆ (702) 328-1219 ◆ Angel.Torres5@va.gov

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Highly organized and detail oriented with Knowledge of various office computer software programs, tools, and techniques to support office operations with over 10 years of experience in fast paced environments who wants to grow and experience new challenges

# **SKILLS**

- Installations and repairs
- Excellent time management
- Basic medical terminologies
- Data entry
- Skilled multi-tasker
- Excellent communication skills
- Computer programs

- Computer operations
- Ability to type 40 wpm
- Initiative quick learner
- Adaptive and creative
- Professional
- Personable & Reliable with over 300 hrs sick leave
- HardWorking

## WORK HISTORY

#### Medical Support Technician, 05/2018 to Current

VA Hospital – North Las Vegas, NV

- Assisted Staff in installing and Updating software that was needed
- Troubleshooted any equipment that was not working properly for further assessment
- Installed/configured proper drivers to equipment that was necessary for proper equipment.
- Monitored Disk Space for all computers on unit for maximum utilization
- Skilled in various computer programs used in hospital such as CPRS, Vista, BCMA, Word, Microsoft and Exel
- Cleaned and maintained equpment such as computers, copy/faxing machines and printers
- Inputted proper I.p , Subnet and Domain Addresses to equipment whenever they were updated
- Knowledge of various Government Computer Equipment that are used In Hospital
- Managed documents by organizing forms, making photocopies, filing records, preparing correspondence and creating reports.
- Entered and updated information into databases quickly and with minimal errors.

Nutrition Assistant, 07/2015 to 05/2018

VA Hospital Nutrition – North Las Vegas, NV

18.95/hr 40 hrs a week

# Supervisor/Ronaldo Garrett

- Maintained equipment used in nutrition facility such as computers, copy/faxing machines and ticket machines
- Completed MSA training on TMS to establish medical support knowledge of codings, duties and responsibilities and scored high on the pretests
- Developed Skills in fact-finding, problem analysis, problem resolutions, and development of concrete action plans to solve basic medical problems.
- Cross trained in nutrition call center to establish clerical and technical skills
- Received calls from patients and nurses and assisted in communicating with patients and nurses needs
- Utilized computers and various technology to ensure proper work efficiency.
- Helped with patients needs and applied basic medical knowledge to be able to get them referred to the proper health professional
- Prepared paperwork and assisted with clerical duties such as answering phones, data entry input and responding to emails.
- Maintained positive relationships with all patients, customers, and coworkers
- Knowledge of various computer programs, tools, and techniques to support office operations and produce a variety of documents such as letters, reports, spreadsheets, databases, and graphs.
- Delivered trays to patients in a timely and efficient manner while recording accurate patients confidential information and time
- Ability to gather, analyze and present facts, communicate effectively, using tact and courtesy and posses the ability to plan, organize work, and meet deadlines
- Worked independently and under guidance to master general clerical tasks.
- Coordinated and consulted with management about time and leave scheduling so work flow can continue efficiently as possible and documented data in paper and onto VA computer
- Provided clerical support to coworkers by copying, faxing and filing documents.
- Reviewed time sheets, prepared attendance reports and processed payroll for office staff.
- Composed sensitive, confidential reports and documentation.
- Used various methods of data collection to research and record data successfully.

Veterans Canteen Service, 07/2013 to 08/2015

VA Hospital – North Las Vegas, NV

12.00/hr 40 hrs a week

#### Supervisor/Rachel Whaley

- Responded to supervisor and customer requests via telephone and email and effectively answered questions and inquiries.
- Entered details such as payments, account information and call logs into the computer system.
- Assisted customers and patients families in finding locations, parkings and guided them towards the proper support stations
- Assisted in time keeping by managing and recording coworkers schedules by maintaining documentation in timekeeping records

- Minimized damage and repair costs through careful management and preventative maintenance
- Communicated with dispatcher, warehouse manager, and customers regarding incoming and outgoing orders and Gathered, logged, and monitored all shipping data using proper written and computer documentation
- Strategically organized merchandise that arrived through shipment using proper methods such as fist in first out
- Assisted coworkers, and customers by answering questions, responding to inquiries and handling telephone requests.
- Answered telephone calls to field inquiries from clients, vendors and various other callers seeking information.
- Managed office inventory by restocking supplies and placing purchase orders to obtain ample stock.
- Reviewed time sheets, prepared attendance reports and processed payroll for office staff on a regular basis.
- Maintained records of material flow, compiling and organizing related data.
- Screened and sorted incoming mail, faxes and deliveries, routing to appropriate personnel.
- Coordinated the distribution of materials to various locations.
- Distributed incoming mail throughout the office.
- Continually sought methods for improving daily operations, communications with clients, recordkeeping and data entry for increased efficiency.

EDUCATION —
EDUCATION —

**Highschool Diploma**: 2011

Lawndale High School - Lawndale, CA

**Associates**: Computer Science And Programming **College Of Southern Nevada** - Las Vegas, NV

- Continuing education in computer science to obtain associates degree
- Continuing education in BioMedical Engineering

#### - Certifications

- Received many employee of the month and excellent customer service certifications
- CIT 101 microsoft certification

## References

- Production Manager/ Joanne Nalicat (702)224-6336
- Supervisor/ Ronaldo Garrett (702)224-6336
- Former manager/ James Calardy (702)791-9000 ext.14649
- Former supervisor/ Francisco Villa (520)370-8113